

UX Researcher + Designer

New York, NY

janepark.me linkedin.com/in/janepark7

janeparkjp@gmail.com

I am a UX Designer + Researcher that produces the most meaningful and relevant experiences to users. My process is grounded in my previous experience in hospitality and education which has taught me that listening and learning from people is the first step to real solutions.

EXPERIENCE

Workshop In Business Organization (WIBO) - UX Researcher + Designer

MARCH 2019 - MAY 2019

- Improved the goals and vision when creating the staff dashboard
- Acted as project manager for a team of 2 by delegating weekly tasks, meeting deadlines, and organized weekly meetings
- Conducted user interviews, usability testing, analysis, synthesis and reporting
- Sketched wireframes and designed lo-fidelity mockups that addressed UX problems uncovered during the research phase

Upside Health - Freelance UX Designer

APRIL 2019

- Assist the evening UX class: help students with projects (research, prototyping, user testing)
- Guide students in debugging and troubleshooting apps and sites
- Provide detailed and helpful feedback on grading assignments

New York Code + Design Academy - Teaching Assistant

SEPTEMBER 2017 - MARCH 2019

- Analyzed existing data and secondary research to inform design direction
- Collaborated with CEO and Head of Product to create a new feature for their mobile app,
 Ouchie, for tracking pain management and history
- Designed and created the new interface for the feature which is currently in development

Marta - Pastry Sous Chef

APRIL 2015 - MAY 2016

- Implemented user research methodologies to develop new pastry menu items
- Interviewed colleagues and executives to improve the process of payroll, inventory, budgeting, product ordering, and food cost analysis
- Managed kitchen staff including hiring and termination, education and training
- Upheld the highest standards in food and sanitation while maintaining open windows of communication between all cooks, management and front of house staff

EDUCATION

BeginEx | UX Design Accelerated Program

New York Code + Design Academy | UX Design, Web Development Intensive

State University of New York at New Paltz | BA, Psychology

University of Huddersfield, UK | Study Abroad Psychology Program

Robert McKee's Storytelling Seminar | 3 Day Seminar on the craft of Storytelling

SKILLS

Interviews

Information architecture

Competitive analysis

Persona

Storytelling

Data synthesization

Card sorting

Wireframing

Prototyping

Usability testing

User flows

TOOLS

Sketch

Figma

Balsamig

InVision

Marvel

Zeplin

Trello

DEVELOPMENT

HTML/CSS

JavaScript

VOLUNTEER

DesignOps Summit 2018

HACKATHONS

HexHacks Nov 2018

BeginEx Design

Hacakthon March 2019